The next standard,
you need to know about him.
Maybe the final standard is ERC 1155.
It was coined the final standard for any of these
on his hair.
And now it's a bold statement.
But basically there was a steam,
the engine team and they built this new smart contract
standard for entities on aetherium.
And basically,
you can think of it as an enhancement of erc721
or a superset of the template.
That was erc721.
Now,
why is it a superset of erc721?
Well,
first of all,
it's cheaper because you can hold asset classes,
it.
No longer tracks singular ownership on erc721.
You interact with a contract and it tracked ownership of
each individual piece.
What this meant was that if you had.
And if he's on an erc721 contract,
let's say you own five assets.
If you wanted to transfer those assets,
you would have to transfer those assets one by one,
right?
And so doing that.
Buy one,
you're paying fees on each individual transaction.
And er c1155.
You can hold asset classes.
So if you if you buy 10 and if tease
of you know,
let's say you buy 10 digital art pieces from the
same project.
Now in,
ER c1155,
you can hold all of those 10 together and you
can sell them together.
You can transfer them together.
It's cheaper.
You don't have to pay as many Gatsby's going back
and forth because you can sell them in bulk.
There's a lot of enhancements,
but it's a super said,
because you can also create an erc721 acid inside
of a smart contract.
That is,
er,
c1155.
This is a complicated mechanism for saying that they're complimentary.
Basically,
they're complimentary.
They're not competition.
Erc721 can support our c1155 but ER c1155
the smart contract,
pipe and support.
Assets of this time.
And so with that,
what you need to know here is that this is
the current standard.
This is where it started.
This is where it's going.
And by knowing that you can,
deep dive a bit deeper into all of the aspects.
I can go into it and I will be linking
the docks to the standard CR c1155 so you can
read a bit deeper about it.
But at the end of the day this is what
most marketplaces are running on right now and how asset
classes are kind of divvied up.
Right?
We we we want things to be cheaper,
faster smarter,
cuz the theorem can cost a lot of money when
you're paying these gas fees,
to transfer things and erc721 did a lot of good
things,
but the enhancements that come from 1155 far,
outweigh the benefits of 7:00,
to 1.
And that's where the trickiness lies.
But basically,
this is the Smart contract type that is now powering
the majority of transactions around,
and if he's on a theorem and now,
What we need to know here.
That is the Crux of it all.