We reach the final stretch.
How do we spell and distribute an nft?
Here you see open?
See a website to discover collect them selves,
extraordinary entities.
It's one of the largest nft marketplaces available and
to simplify the process to entry without needing to build
your own smart contract.
Deploy your own code,
learn how to code.
And all of that in-between.
We're going to use Open Sea to create our own
mfp.
But you will need an aetherium wallet to use
open sea.
And so,
like we said,
aetherium is powering a lot of the energy market and
if these are in huge demand and open sea is
a Marketplace that built on top of aetherium to make
it easy for you to sell distribute and even by
your own interpeace.
Now,
we're going to go specifically through how to open your
own wallet and sell on the Open Sea.
Let's get start.