Now that we know what,
and if these are right and what the difference is
between a fungible and a non-fungible asset.
We can definitely have to ask her a question.
Why,
why do we need?
And if peace to do anything at all?
What is the purpose of a saying?
Okay.
Well,
we know what,
a fungible acid as we know what a non-fungible asset
is,
but why do we need these tokens to Define ownership,
right?
And,
you know,
at the end of the day,
that's a great question.
So,
let's talk about purpose,
right?
Let's talk about purpose in a digital world in the
digital world ownership was never clearly defined.
What I mean by this was never clearly defined honestly,
like,
when I bought something,
I knew I was the owner of it yet.
You knew,
but was it public?
Did you have the sole rights to that item?
Is it traceable?
Write all of those things just like,
only a watch.
I know that's my watch.
I know that I bought that watch.
Therefore.
That is my watch,
right.
Yeah,
but like,
what actually makes it your watch is it tracked in
the database somewhere?
Does Rolex keep a database of the serial number against
the,
the person who bought it?
Maybe they do,
maybe they do a knuckleball Define ownership,
right?
The serial codes often do the fine order ship,
but only if their track against the purchaser.
So,
in a digital world,
Do we get serial codes on things?
Well,
think of a time,
where you bought a domain name,
a game skin,
a ticket,
right?
Just purchasing online in general makes all the difference in
the world.
Because,
you know,
you're purchasing a domain name is very traceable.
Right?
Like I cannot is tracking this person bought it and
we have whoisguard.
So there is a database tracking,
who is the rightful owner of the domain name.
Can I resell it?
Not really.
Well,
I can resell my domain,
but there's no real mechanism for it.
It's more.
So a transferability aspect and then someone,
you know,
pays me for.
There's no real on my mechanism that really warms fat
in a easy-to-use way.
Think of a game skin.
Have you ever played fortnite?
Although you buy that skin,
you know what,
it's linked to your account.
Therefore.
There is a form of ownership,
right?
A certain form.
But can I go and resell it on eBay?
Can I take that skin?
And you don't turn a profit?
It's quite difficult to ask a question.
Do you actually own it?
And ownership means that you can freely resell the good.
You own.
Right,
it does mean that,
right?
Like,
if I own something like,
if I buy a watch,
I have the physical good.
I go to a store,
I say,
hey,
how much and they give me money and I give
them the watch.
If I buy a game skin online on fortnite or
whatever other game,
you may play doesn't have to be 49,
but any game at all,
it's really difficult to resell it.
Like I can't just going for the price tag on
it.
Now,
there were certain games in the past that allowed this
ability of reselling skins,
right?
There was a csgo stuff that went on in there
have been ways of doing this,
right?
But all of those ways,
we're kind of proprietary like they weren't unified think of
it like this.
A market place to sell these digital things was usually
built custom to the asset.
That was being sold for the 10 unified way to
track ownership of any digital good whatsoever,
doesn't matter what it is.
And that exactly is what.
And if keys are trying to solve the right to
ownership the right to resell,
and they're enabling that through different mechanisms in those mechanisms
will talk about.
But the why of entities the why is the ownership
part the ownership of being very strict and through that
ownership enabling ways to clearly Define that
resale ability.
Because when we ask ourselves,
what's my proof today?
Is it an email?
Is it like a thread is the serial number?
Yeah,
maybe maybe it's all of those things.
But is it publicly traced?
No?
Is it clear know and all those questions?
All those problems are what NFP as a technology is
trying to solve know if we take nft as a
technology,
right?
Just don't brawl technology like the concept of an if
keep the token that represents the non-fungible item.
That is the y,
That's the ownership part and then through concept we
get into.
All right,
how do I enable that?
And that's when we enter blockchain a decentralized ledger,
right?
Blockchain technology again,
a technology that enables other Concepts other Technologies to build
upon it.
And that's what most men on.
But what I want to end on is that the
why of non-fungible tokens is for that proof of ownership
and through that proof of ownership,
having that Tolkien being able to say,
I own this asset and being able to enable me.
Places,
treatability,
resale ability.
All of those things we can do that now because
the concept is there,
a generic concept not a proprietary concept where Call of
Duty has its own Marketplace and fortnite has its own
Marketplace.
That means every company needs to build their own proprietary
system.
And if these enable a generic system that everyone can
build upon doesn't matter what company,
leverage the generic blockchain technology and enable resale ability without
needing to build all of the systems in a closed-off
way.