Now that we have a collection and we have it
all set up with everything that we need.
Right?
We have our own personal profile does eating profile.
We now have a collection on the market place.
The collection on the market place,
isn't the end of Kezia.
It's just Open,
Seas way of pulling together.
All of the items that you want on there.
What you would call a project.
So,
your art pieces,
you can put in different collection if you wanted to
make specific elections for specific things.
So now let's go ahead and add an item over
here.
You can see the create a new item form.
This is where open allows us to actually,
upload our image or video or MP3,
whatever the case may be.
And so,
what we're going to upload is our very first,
and if he does etm biker,
and we're going to call him this etm biker.
So here you can see the uploaded you can do,
jpg,
PNG,
GIF,
SVG MP3 all of the above.
And if you have a project externally,
right?
If you have a bigger project where you have a
website with all the information on the art,
you're trying to make you can link the specific item
with extra information so that they can go view your
project.
Now over here,
you can fill in the description here will fill in
the very first ztm,
nft.
Ztm biker.
And then we'll add it to the collection 02 Mastery.
Cuz that's the only connection we have.
And here,
you can see that.
You can add properties to it,
right?
You get out of properties,
like character age,
all that stuff.
So what we're going to do is we'll give it
a character.
But we're going to call the character number one,
cuz the very first NFL team.
Can get a level,
we can give its that,
you could even give it unlock.
Apple content,
unlockable content being specific,
access key,
and email something to contact someone or a specific item
code that you could redeem for something and who knows?
Maybe we'll put something in here.
So that's where you can put unlockable content.
Next to that you can mark it as explicit content
just in case.
It's not for young people and you can determine on
what blockchain.
So open see supports aetherium and polygon polygon is a
gas free.
Block Chain experience that works with aetherium.
So you can determine on which chain you basically want
to sell it and then once you hit create you
created,
But once you hit create,
it actually goes through the process of creating your nft
on the Open Sea platform.
Now at that point it had been distributed to the
marketplace just yet.
It just says you created the ztm biker.